(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-25T13:24:43.724020",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
hololive English 4th Concert Serendipity - 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
Greetings, CeCe, my fated rival!
Greetings, CeNa, my distant rival!
And hello to everyone...
Everyone watching from
Serendipity! Woo!
Remember, if you want a chance for your wish to be featured on the Ootomu or the Takotachi that we made,
post the bottle with hashtag WishUponTakoTomo!
Yay! Thank you, AmiAmi, for supporting our rivalry,
and for supporting Serendipity! Be sure to check out their booth at
Anime Expo!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
Hey, powballs!
It's Shirakami Fubuki,
Ookami Mio,
Koseki Bijou,
Otonose Kanade,
Shiranui Flare,
Himemori Luna,
Tsunomaki Watame,
Kikirara Vivi,
Yukihana Lamy,
Hakui Koyori,
AZKi,
La+ Darknesss,
all 14 of us!
hololive BASE is coming to ROUND1 USA locations nationwide, starting this September!
Come hang out with us! Follow @round1usa on Instagram and X so you don't miss out on any updates!
Bye-bye!
Attention For Visitors
The concert will be starting soon.
A-D-V-E-N-T
Everyone! Let's light the fire!
Time to get this party started!
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, as you desire
Chasing all that we aspire
Spreading out like wildfire
Never ever, have I ever
Been a sinner, been a dreamer
Take the chance and with my lighter
Start the fire
Come pull me out
I'm out of sheep to count
This overkill of sad old story is wearing me down
Snap out of the system
Break out give it everything
This is our time
We're yours to discover
Hello, brand new world
Would you welcome the light?
And free us from the night
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, as you desire
Ignite our beating hearts
Dance into the flame of life
Dance until the end of time
Rebellion
Time to get this party started!
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, as you desire
Chasing all that we aspire
I know that I can still be
The future of this story
I know that I can be free
The one and the only
They tell me that I'm crazy
I'll never let them stop me
With this, our advent begins!
Time to get this party started!
Never ever, have I ever
Been a sinner, been a dreamer
Fire, fire, light the fire
Ignite these beating hearts
Jump into the stream of life
Jump until the end of time
Dance into the flame of life
Dance until the end of time
Rebellion
Time to get this party started!
Fire, fire, light the fire
Brighter, higher, as you desire
Time to get this party started!
Don't, don't know me, unpredictable
Takin' you all below, takin' you all below
Don't, don't know me, irresistible
Takin' you all below, below we go
They think they want it? Huh?
They wanna ge-get down
We take 'em down, down, down
Queendom in the borderline
Run it, no surprise
You ain't gonna win but you can try
Told ya, you got no luck
End up in my lineup, listen, listen
Run, oh, hide and scream out, already locked ya up
Fool's games you always play
Call me corrupt, won't hear anything
Aiming my sight down right on your heart
Throwin' the keys out, shut down, i-i-i
Justice, love it, the forbidden
Just like that, you're never forgiven
Justice, not one to just forget
Get, get that, we got 'em
The higher I rise, down further you dive
Stand in' on the edge, don't know me, unpredictable, typical, you got nowhere to go
Show you somethin' real, my level no you'll never know
As above so below
You should know
Run in the light, oh, my dio
What's wrong, what's right?
Rushin' in a fantasy, wanna be disease
Sure that you won't ever make it out
Eyes follow now
Do it, do it
New target locked on it now
Enemies? Girl, I lost count
See your guilty heart
We're not gonna stop, it's just the start
Get down, get da-ra-da
Like it like that? Run it like that
Get down
Takin' me up, up, up, let's go
Goin' above, go below
Told ya, you already know
Don't ya
Run in the light, oh, my dio
What's wrong, what's right with you?
Run in the night, oh, my dio
Come take a bite
Never ending, endless sky
(Get it, get it, get it, get it)
(Justice just like that, Justice get get that)
If you're feeling trapped, send out a signal right above!
(Gesundheit!)
We'll find you, set you free then you can sign up for the club!
(In it!)
Danger, fun, fun, fun
No sad, say bye, bye
(Minna happiness, minna happiness)
The frig? I'm big! My strong, strong muscle
They see me run, it's no miracle
You are shining
So bright!
Do your dancing
Let's fight!
You can be a
Super, super girl
I'm the
Super!
(Hey!)
Duper!
(Supernova super girl)
Super!
(Hey!)
Duper!
(Supernova super girl)
Come sing with us, beating villains for fun <3 it
Put on your antennas, get your super girl fit
Super!
(Hey!)
Duper!
Supernova super girl
I always want a pizza, stack those fries up to the sky
(Ciao, ciao)
You lot say whatcha think about us hittin' town tonight?
(Justice!)
Feeling happy time
No sad, say bye, bye
(Motto maniac, justice just like that)
So stomp, stomp, stomp your feet to this beat
Cuz we are space, no, no gravity!
You are shining
So bright!
Do your dancing
Let's fight!
You can be a
Super, super girl
I'm the
Super!
(Hey!)
Duper!
(Supernova super girl)
Super!
(Hey!)
Duper!
(Supernova super girl)
I know you're feeling so super bad
You don't have depression, you're just super sad
We are change the world,
That's hope!
If you doubt, hope you
Explode!
Justice loud, justice proud
And we keep telling you!
Baby, how's your life?
Are you living free?
Let's forget everything and have some fun
Chu chu chu
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice, here we just play dice!
Baby, baby there's no need to think twice
Dari wari woah
Make it your night, make it your fight, make it your spotlight
Get out from the hamster wheel and rule your life
5 4 3 2 1 play dice!
(Hey, hey) (Bae, bae)
Baby~
So the space went “bang” and we were all born,
The order we knew, ripped and torn.
But we have no time to complain
'Cause life is short, can't do it over again.
If we can laugh, it doesn't matter where or when
Be ji chuu hon pou
Physics don't play the dice?
So let trouble stir and rise!
Be limits, bounds, rules or chains… imi nante na a a i
So we don't give a chu
Ya na koto wa sotto mute
So find something new
Karada juu isshun de muchuu ha!
No cage can trap this rat (Bae!)
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice, here we just play dice!
Yell and scream come on now, don't be too nice
Dari wari woah
Follow your heart, pump your fist up, come and join the club
Go and scream for you the one who's flying free
Kaosu no daisu no mama de ii
For this moment i am truly really me!
5 4 3 2 1 play dice!
Blah blah blah blah nandra kandra
Blah blah blah blah rati rata rat rat
Blah blah blah blah
Now here i will recite to you
The only thing that will hold true
Yolo is my ninja way
It's time put those moves out there on display
Why stress about tomorrow when you've got today?
Be yo chuu shaku shaku
Ima ga saikou ka saitei ka nante daremo shiranai
Jinsei so sei chuu seitte maji de mijika a a i
Wow, aren't we sick as chu?
Wareware tte egii cute
So rush on to our route
Hanabi hashira se marude denryuu ha!
No math can settle this rat (Bae!)
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice, here we just play dice!
Come and venture into my dope dumpsite
Dari wari woah
Time to run and follow our sun, won't stop till we're done
Idiots are allowed infinite fun
Minna jiyuu ja nakya mottainai jan
It's never too late, our journey's just begun!
If you hesitate on what to do, that's it, game over. You are screwed.
Naite mo waratte mo chu chu chu
Baby, baby, it's our time!
(Chu chu chu)
Here we roll dice, here we cast dice, here we just play dice!
Baby, baby, there's no need to think twice
Dari wari woah
This is our night, this is our fight, this is our spotlight
Before giving in, go show them your best try!
Koukai shichattara mou iki kirenai!
Whatchu doing bruh go out and live your life!
5 4 3 2 1 play dice!
Hey hey my bae / Baby don't care
Hey hey my bae / Bae don't be scared
(Now sing baby?)
Blah blah blah blah nandra kandra
Blah blah blah blah rati rata rat rat
Blah blah blah blah
The days are blending together
Pretending like i don't notice
Drowning in mental fog so thick my hands might close where my throat is
I'm not gonna rap that "i'm cursed"
My words got heavy
And sure enough the steady ebb-and-flow of life subsided, but i wasn't ready
Last night, i thought up a song
But i'm too wired to hum it
Inspired sight, like tunnel vision on the life i got from it
Not tired yet, right? ha
It's fun, i'll tell you that much
Adventures oughta be remembered as such
But, i'm not well
Not today, not tomorrow
These souls inside my pocket are just sanity i borrow
"Sayonara" to the sorrow of eternity alone?
Yeah, right
Part of the joke is that it's all that i've known
base instincts take control
like primal ways of a warrior
is it glory you're after, like me?
underestimated everywhere I turn
taking aim but it doesn't make a difference at all
I got a million different enemies I cannot recall
you're rocking up to a battle when you know that you'll fall
hidden motivation, watch it all burn
I gotta tell you
I never liked you
now would I lie to you?
let me ignite you
when thunder crashes down
when the world caves under my pressure
there'll be no one to save
where is your pride, your human will to survive?
was it just
empty words for your grave?
I reach inside this soul
now all that remains
is delusion and decay
cuz of you, I live this way
we're not rivals
we're not equals
you're just confused
lightning never strikes twice in the same spot
so go ahead and run up on me till you get your shot
I see the weapon that you're hiding, come on ready or not
another life and you would never give a second thought
thinkin' your pride's different than mine
ticking all your vital signs off
but we still gotta protect all our friends from our enemies
wouldn't you agree?
forged in fires of hell
god can't betray you
if I'm a fallen angel
what does that make you?
I'm not debasing myself
to see the same view
when it's your pride on the line
no one can save you from mine
we're not rivals
we're not equals
base instincts take control
like primal ways of a warrior
is it glory you're after, like me?
underestimated everywhere I turn
taking aim but it doesn't make a difference at all
I got a million different enemies I cannot recall
you're rocking up to a battle when you know that you'll fall
hidden motivation, watch it all burn
I gotta tell you
I never liked you
now would I lie to you?
let me ignite you
when thunder crashes down
when the world caves under my pressure
there'll be no one to save
where is your pride, your human will to survive?
was it just
empty words for your grave?
I reach inside this soul
now all that remains
is delusion and decay
cuz of you, I live this way
we're not rivals
we're not equals
you're just confused
lightning never strikes twice in the same spot
so go ahead and run up on me till you get your shot
I see the weapon that you're hiding, come on ready or not
another life and you would never give a second thought
thinkin' your pride's different than mine
ticking all your vital signs off
but we still gotta protect all our friends from our enemies
wouldn't you agree?
forged in fires of hell
god can't betray you
if I'm a fallen angel
what does that make you?
I'm not debasing myself
to see the same view
when it's your pride on the line
no one can save you from mine
we're not rivals
we're not equals
thinkin' your pride's different than mine
ticking all your vital signs off
but we still gotta protect all our friends from our enemies
wouldn't you agree?
taking aim but it doesn't make a difference at all
I got a million different enemies I cannot recall
you're rocking up to a battle when you know that you'll fall
hidden motivation, watch it all burn
I gotta tell you
I never liked you
now would I lie to you?
let me ignite you
when thunder crashes down
when the world caves under my pressure
there'll be no one to save
where is your pride, your human will to survive?
was it just
empty words for your grave?
I reach inside this soul
now all that remains
is delusion and decay
cuz of you, I live this way
close up to your little thin veil
when thunder crashes down
we're not rivals
we're not equals
lately I realized I would never be, never be alone
it was always right in front of me
do you know, do you remember, remember
how we used to be so carefree
oh, hey
I can feel the rain wash over
I can feel the rain wash over you
Oh, hey
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down, trembling voice
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in
And I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Can't make them stop, hidden sparks inside ignite and flare up
And when we talk, all my secrets spilling over the top
So when I step up to your side and my heart is beating in double time
In every moment you make me feel alive, it goes like
I can feel the rain wash over you
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down, trembling voice
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in
And I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Ha ha ha! Ha!
Hello, hello!
Hello there!
Hello, hello, hello, hello!
Hello up there!
Hello down there!
Hello everyone!
Hey, who are you?
Hi, darlings!
This is Hololive English Advent's devilish diva,
the one, the only, Nerissa Ravencroft!
And with me...
Roses are red, the fire in my heart is blue,
also known as the Scarlet Queen, the harbinger of order, leader of justice, I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Lovely to see you, to see you!
Lovely!
So, so far!
Wow, what a setlist thus far, huh?
Yeah, we're starting off really strong!
We had...
Sneaker, Sneaker!
Oh my god!
And we had Mori rocking it out, seriously!
And then Kronii coming in with her new song, so good!
Yeah! Such cute dance moves.
And we had Advent and Justice, of course.
Yes, yes. Did you enjoy? Did you enjoy?
And hey, did you enjoy?
Yeah, music as well!
Wow, you know what, we didn't have solos yesterday. Oh, no, so we must be having them today, right?
So exciting!
Oh, yeah, for mine, I want to practice something, okay?
A little chant from great Exordia.
So when I go "Ogi ogi ogi", you go "Oi, oi, oi"!
Are you ready? Okay, here we go!
Ogi ogi ogi! Oi, oi, oi!
Perfect. Cumpekki. Cumpekki?
Did you guys have any sneak peeks about your solo?
Mm...
Would you guys really like a sneak peek?
Wow, uh, I think I have to remind you all, no matter how you identify, no matter what you are, you in this audience today are my wives.
Can I hear from my wives?
What the freak, everyone here is your wife? Including you?
So, if I ask you to sing along, you have to, all right? You're going to...
Just to give it away, maybe a little.
I'd love to hear you guys sing too.
You guys know I like harmonies. Yes!
So we're gonna split you into different notes, okay?
So we have you guys over here,
you guys over here,
and all of you at the top.
So, we're gonna start off with you guys here.
We want you to hold this note.
Ah...
Perfect.
You guys, ah...
Up there, ah...
All right, everyone together!
Ah-ah-ah, ah...
Beautiful, beautiful!
Oh, my gosh! We're our own choir!
So good!
We gotta do that more often, that was cool!
Yeah!
I like hearing you all sing for us.
Hey, that reminds me of a song, doesn't it?
You know that, that first note?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, something like... Three, two, one.
It's wonderous, somehow we met along the way.
Now here you are beside me, embracing serendipity.
Oh, wow, that was great, wasn't it?
Harmonizing, yes!
It's wonderful harmonizing with you.
And I just want to say thank you so much for being my friend.
I love you!
Anyway, we're gonna sing together!
Yeah, you're gonna sing together!
I got too excited!
I'm just too happy!
I'm so happy, too!
Ah, I spam too fast, there we go.
Anyway, Mudia-haishin ma, tsugi no kyoku desu!
Saigo ni narimasu!
The YouTube free sneak peek is only until the next song, which is a duet!
If you want to continue watching, click the link in the description and get your tickets now!
All right, everybody...
After three, we all say Serendipity, got it?
Yeah!
Oh, thanks so very much.
We love you guys so much!
We love you!
All right, here we go!
Three, two, one, Serendipity!
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
Nerissa Ravencroft
Bloodraven
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame / Nerissa Ravencroft
残酷な天使のように
Zankoku na tenshi no you ni
少年よ神話になれ
Shounen yo shinwa ni nare
蒼い風がいま
Aoi kaze ga ima
胸のドアを叩いても
mune no doa wo tataitemo
私だけをただ見つめて
Watashi dake wo tada mitsumete
微笑んでるあなた
hohoendeiru anata
そっとふれるもの
Sotto fureru mono
求めることに夢中で
motomeru koto ni muchuu de
運命さえまだ知らない
Unmei sae mada shiranai
いたいけな瞳
itaiikena hitomi
だけどいつか気づくでしょう
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
その背中には
Sono se ni wa
遥か未来めざすための
haruka mirai mezasu tame no
羽根があること
hane ga aru koto
残酷な天使のテーゼ
Zankoku na tenshi no thesis
窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
Madobe kara hayate ni tobitatsu
ほとばしる熱いパトスで
Hotobashiru atsui pathos de
思い出を裏切るなら
Omoide wo uragiru nara
この宇宙を抱いて輝く
Kono uchuu wo daki-shime hikaru
少年よ神話になれ
Shounen yo shinwa ni nare
眠る別れからやがて飛び立つ
Nemuru wakare kara yagate tobidatsu
この空を 抱いて輝く 少年よ神話になれ
Be a myth, young boy who shines, embracing this sky!
蒼く眠ってる 私の愛のゆりかご
Sleeping in blue, the cradle of my love,
あなただけが 夢の使者に 呼ばれる朝が来る
the morning will come when only you are called by the messenger of dreams.
細い首筋を 月明かりが映し出してる
Moonlight illuminates your slender neck.
世界中の時間を止めて 閉じ込めたいけど
I want to stop all the time in the world and lock it away, but...
もしも二人出逢えたことに意味があるなら
If there is meaning in the two of us meeting,
私はそう自由を知るためのバイブル
I am a bible for knowing true freedom.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 悲しみがそして始まる
A cruel angel's thesis, and then sorrow begins.
抱きしめた命の形 その夢に目覚めた時
When you awake to the form of the life you embraced in that dream,
誰よりも光を放つ 少年よ神話になれ
shining brighter than anyone else, be a myth, young boy!
人は愛を紡ぎながら 歴史を作る
People spin love while making history.
女神なんてなれないまま 私は生きる
Staying unable to become a goddess, I live on.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
A cruel angel's thesis, soon flying out from the windowsill.
ほとばしる熱いパトスで 思い出を裏切るなら
If you betray memories with gushing, passionate pathos,
この空を 抱いて輝く 少年よ神話になれ
be a myth, young boy who shines, embracing this sky!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.